repairwin.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy • Repair Windows™

**Privacy Policy**

At this website “www.repairwin.com”, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use [www.repairwin.com](http://www.repairwin.com/) and how it is used.

**Repairwin.com** adopts best practice in compliance with applicable privacy law and regulations, including the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”).

This Policy is only applicable to this site (www.repairwin.com) and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy.

**BY ACCESSING, USING AND/OR DOWNLOADING THE SITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AND ALSO SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF OUR  [TERMS OF SERVICE](https://www.repairwin.com/terms-of-service/). IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT ACCESS, DOWNLOAD AND/OR USE THE SITE**. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy frequently, as it may change from time to time. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use the Site.

**How we collect or obtain information about you**

  1. When you provide it to us (e.g. by contacting us or when commenting to a post/article)
  2. When visiting our website (e.g. from Usage Data, Logs and Cookies).

**What Information we collect**

  1. The name and your email address (only if you provide them to us) when you communicate with us, by using the contact form or when commenting to an article..
  2. Our website server records some anonymous information regarding user's visit sent by the web browser. No personal data is collected, the server only collects general information such as your IP address, information from cookies, information about your device type (e.g. computer or mobile), the browser you use, which pages you visited and when you visited them and your geographical location (based on your IP address).

**How we use your information**

  1. To reply to you when posting a comment or when contacting us using the [contact form](https://www.repairwin.com/contact/).
  2. For administrative purposes only, like to improve this website, to analyze the use of our website and in connection with our legal rights and obligations.

**How we secure your information**  
This website takes all the appropriate security measures such as storing your information on secure servers, encrypting transfers of data to or from our servers using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. We recommend that you use anti-virus software, anti-malware, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats. If you become aware of any breach of Site security or this Privacy Policy, please notify us immediately.

**SPAM protection  
**This type of services analyzes the traffic of this Website, potentially containing Users’ Personal Data, with the purpose of filtering it from parts of traffic, messages and content that are recognized as SPAM. ** **

In this website we use the following SPAM Protection services:

  * **Akismet (Automattic Inc.)  
**Akismet is a SPAM protection service provided by [Automattic Inc](https://automattic.com/).  
**Personal Data collected:** various types of Data as specified in the [privacy policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/) of the service.  
**Place of processing:** United States – [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/).

  * **Google reCAPTCHA (Google Inc.)  
**Google reCAPTCHA is a SPAM protection service provided by Google Inc.  
The use of reCAPTCHA is subject to the Google [privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and [terms of use](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/).  
**Personal Data collected:** Cookies and Usage Data.  
**Place of processing:** United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

**Share of information:  
**We do not disclose, sell or provide your personal data that you have submitted through comments or through our [contact form](https://www.repairwin.com/contact/), in any way to third parties.

**_Disclosure of your information to third parties_** : Only to the extent necessary to run our business, to our service providers and where required by law or to enforce our legal rights.

**How long we retain your information  
**If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

**Cookies**  
This website use cookies to store information about visitors' preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.  
Cookies help us learn which areas of our Site are useful and which areas need improvement through programs including, but not limited to Google Analytics.  
Promotions or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our site.

**Google Analytics  
**Like other websites, we also use Google Analytics service to understand the traffic coming towards our website and to make our website better. It helps us in understanding how visitors use our website so that we can improve their experience.

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

**Personal Data collected:** Cookies and Usage Data.  
**Place of processing:** US – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

**What are your choices regarding cookies.**  
You may opt-out from Google’s cookies using their [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated). You may also use the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt-out of some third party cookies.  
If you’d like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.  
Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.

  * For the Chrome web browser, please visit this page from Google: <https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050>
  * For the Internet Explorer web browser, please visit this page from Microsoft: <http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835>
  * For the Firefox web browser, please visit this page from Mozilla: <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored>
  * For the Safari web browser, please visit this page from Apple: <https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?locale=en_US>
  * For any other web browser, please visit your web browser’s official web pages.

**Where can you find more information about cookies.  
**You can learn more about cookies and the following third-party websites:

  * AllAboutCookies: <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>
  * Network Advertising Initiative: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>

**Third Party Advertising  
**In this website we use third party advertisements in order to financially support the site. Some of these ads might make use of tools such as web beacons and cookies that could potentially also send these advertisers certain information like the web browser you are using to visit the site, whether you have flash installed on your system, your IP (internet protocol), or your ISP (Internet Service Provider). Personally identifiable information data, like name, address, email, phone number or similar are NOT included.

Some of our digital advertising service providers are members of the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance, each of which offer a single location to opt-out of certain ad targeting from member companies. To learn more about interest-based advertising generally as well as your options for opting out, please visit [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) or [About Ads](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). In addition, the Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own website at [FTC Privacy Site](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/topics/privacy-identity). Please keep in mind that even if you opt-out of receiving ads tailored to your apparent interests, you will continue to see ads from online advertising networks. However, those networks will not be able to apply any of your apparent ad preferences and the ads that you see therefore may be less relevant to your interests.

  * **DoubleClick DART Cookie.  
**Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this Website.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this Website and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>  
You can use [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/) to manage the Google ads you see and opt out of Ads Personalization.
  * **Adsense  
**On this website, the controller has integrated Google AdSense. Google AdSense is an online service which allows the placement of advertising on third-party sites. Google AdSense is based on an algorithm that selects advertisements displayed on third-party sites to match with the content of the respective third-party site. Google AdSense allows an interest-based targeting of the Internet user, which is implemented by means of generating individual user profiles.  
The operating company of Google’s AdSense component is Alphabet Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, United States.  
Through Google AdSense, personal data and information—which also includes the IP address, and is necessary for the collection and accounting of the displayed advertisements—is transmitted to Alphabet Inc. in the United States of America. These personal data will be stored and processed in the United States of America. The Alphabet Inc. may disclose the collected personal data through this technical procedure to third parties.  
Google AdSense is further explained under the following link <https://www.google.com/intl/en/adsense/start/>.
  * **CJ Affiliate by Conversant  
**CJ Affiliate by Conversant (formerly Commission Junction) is a affiliate marketing network, specializing in pay-for-performance programs that drive results for businesses around the world.  
**Personal Data collected:** Cookies and Usage Data.  
For more details, please review their [Privacy Policy](https://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy).

**Interaction with external social networks and platforms.  
**This type of service allows interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Website.  
The interaction and information obtained through this Website are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.  
This type of service might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

To interact with other platforms we use the following services:

  * **Google+ +1 button and social widgets (Google Inc.)  
**The Google+ +1 button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Google+ social network provided by Google Inc.  
**Personal Data collected:** Cookies and Usage Data.  
**Place of processing:** United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/privacy/). Privacy Shield participant.

  * **Facebook Like button and social widgets (Facebook, Inc.)  
**The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.  
**Personal Data collected:** Cookies and Usage Data.  
**Place of processing:** United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation).

  * **LinkedIn –**[ **"Share on LinkedIn" Plugin button**](https://www.linkedin.com/help/linkedin/answer/521/adding-the-share-on-linkedin-plugin?lang=en) **.  
**The ["Share on LinkedIn" Plugin button](https://www.linkedin.com/help/linkedin/answer/521/adding-the-share-on-linkedin-plugin?lang=en) and social widgets are allowing interaction with the LinkedIn professional network provided by LinkedIn Corporation.  
**Personal Data collected:** Cookies and Usage Data. [Cookie Policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie_policy?src=li-other&veh=www.linkedin.com) – [Privacy Policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?trk=hb_ft_priv)

  * **Twitter Tweet button and social widgets (Twitter, Inc.)  
**The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter, Inc.  
**Personal Data collected:** Cookies and Usage Data.  
**Place of processing:** United States – [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy).

  * **Paypal.**  
In this website we have integrated the Paypal Donate button for donations from our users. We recommend that you read [Paypal’s privacy policy](https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full) prior to effecting any transactions with us.

**Gravatar  
**We use the Gravatar service provided by Automattic inc. When visitors leave comments on the site an anonymized string created from their email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service. After approval of the comment, the profile picture which is provided by Gravatar will be publicly visible in the context of the comment. For information about Gravatar and how it collects and processes data, please visit its privacy policy: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>

**Jetpack  
**We use Jetpack, a tool for statistical evaluation of accesses by visitors that is operated by Automattic, Inc., using a tracking technology by Quantcast Inc. You can opt-out to the collection and use of the data by Quantcast at <https://www.quantcast.com/opt-out/>. You can find out more about how Jetpack and Quantacast collect and process data by visiting their respective privacy policy pages at <https://jetpack.com/support/privacy/> and <https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/>

**Traffic Optimization  
**We use Stackpath as a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by StackPath LLC. The way Stackpath is integrated means that it filters parts of the traffic through this Website, i.e., communication between this Website and the User's browser, while also allowing analytical data from this Website to be collected. For information about Stackpath and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://www.stackpath.com/privacy-statement/)

**Links to Third Party Websites  
**We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites might differ from our own.

**Transfers of your information outside the European Economic Area** : in certain circumstances we transfer your information outside of the European Economic Area, including to the United States of America. Where we do so, we will ensure appropriate safeguards are in place, including, for example, that the third parties we use who transfer your information outside the European Economic Area have self-certified themselves as compliant with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield.

**Your rights in relation to your information**

  1. To get a copy of your stored personal data we hold about you.
  2. To erase your personal data.

Notice: This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

**Notice concerning children.  
**

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time discussing with minors their online activity, so as to be fully familiar with the websites they visit and the apps they use. Our Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Site. If you are under 13, do not use this Site, register an Account, or provide any information about yourself to us. If we discover that we have received any personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will take reasonable steps to delete that information as quickly as possible.

**Hosting.  
**This website is currently hosted in the United States. We are hosted on a server provided by HawkHost inc. For information about HawkHost and how it collects and processes data, please visit its [Privacy Policy](https://www.hawkhost.com/Legal/privacy).

**Changes to this privacy policy.  
**The owner of this website reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy if necessary and without obligation to provide you with prior information. We encourage users to periodically check this page to ensure you are familiar with the most current version.

**Contact.  
**If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, or would like to make any requests in relation to your Personal Information, please feel free to contact us by using this [contact form](https://www.repairwin.com/contact/).

**Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to its privacy policy and agree to its [terms of service](https://www.repairwin.com/terms-of-service/). If you do not agree, you must immediately stop using our website.

**Last update:** May 29, 2018
